We will fly all over the world, all
over the sky, all over time.
And found
the secret…
4.1
"CHRISTMAS IN NEVERLAND"
Not bad at all, huh, Michael?
Not bad?
You mean it's the most beautiful tree in
the world!
Just one last touch and...
Sorry, it's gonna have to wait a little
longer.
Mom and Dad won't let us use the
stepladder.
Who ever heard of a tree without a
star?
So forget about the stepladder.
It's too dangerous.
Well, I want a star!
Michael!
And I'm gonna have one!
Um, Michael?
No!
Huh?
Excellent!
That's the first time I've caught a shooting
star!
Peter!
Shooting star?
You said it.
It shot right out of Michael's fingers.
I almost did it!
Peter, since you can fly, would you help
us out and put the star on the
top of the tree?
Oh no, that's not my job.
What?
I don't feel like it.
You'll just have to do it yourself.
Wow!
Did you see that, Wendy?
I put the star on top and it's
perfect!
Did you see me?
Yeah, perfect.
That is not what I look like.
Are you ready to go to Neverland?
Um, you see, it's Christmas and we sort
of decided to try to catch Santa Claus
by surprise and...
Well then, if you want to surprise him,
you better hurry up or else he'll get
to Neverland before us.
Huh?
What?
Santa Claus will be stopping by any minute
now.
He comes to Neverland every year right before
Christmas to pick up some supplies.
You...
you know Santa Claus?
Of course I do.
Don't you?
Want me to introduce him to you?
Yes!
Awesome!
Let's go!
Come on, hurry up!
Like, right now!
Come on, Wendy!
Let's go meet Santa!
Yeah!
Hey, wait for me!
Is Santa Claus nice?
Yeah, I mean, if you've been a good
boy.
I've been pretty good.
Do you think I've been good enough?
Yeah, Michael.
Really?
You think so?
Uh, yep.
Totally, Michael.
I'm gonna get the best present ever!
Yep.
To Neverland!
Let's see...
The thrilling life...
Oh, yes!
Full of adventures that are not the least
bit boring, despite what some people might think.
Of the famous Captain Hook!
No, no, no!
What's all that ruckus?
I'm sorry, but can you believe it?
Captain Hook had the most terrifying crew that
sailed the 15 seas.
No, the wildest crew!
Not bad in the wild, but that's still
not it.
Let's see...
Fearsome, intrepid, courageous...
Oh, please, Jarrow!
Don't you have any taste?
A blue garland coupled with red Christmas balls!
Well, that's...
that's sacrilege!
Yeah, well, uh...
Who's the one that decorated it with red
balls, huh?
Not me!
Stupidest.
That's it.
Stupidest is the right word.
Captain!
Shaloon hit me!
Liar!
He started it by not letting me put
the star on top, and it's my turn
to do it!
If that's how it's gonna be, then the
Captain will set the star on top, and
the Captain will select the garland, because the
Captain has very fine taste.
So there!
Well, uh, silver or gold, Captain?
What?
This is ridiculous!
You pirates!
Blast it!
Indeed!
So red would be the better choice.
Much more pirate, isn't that so, Cap?
I couldn't care less!
A pirate doesn't celebrate Christmas!
Chuck that tree overboard and drop the subject
entirely!
It's enough that Santa Claus comes to scuff
at us every single year!
But, Captain, it's Christmas.
Everyone celebrates Christmas, don't they?
Oh, really?
Well, I hate Christmas!
And this year, no one will celebrate it,
and that's final!
We won't celebrate Christmas.
I hope he manages to land on the
strip this year.
I doubt it.
Santa is no better a pilot than Stringbean
is a tightrope walker.
Yes, but this year, the landing will go
off without a hitch, thanks to yours truly,
Stringbean's wide-ranging knowledge of aeronauto-sleigh-driving
-autics.
Hey, guys!
Huh?
He's here!
He's finally here!
Whoa!
Now that's a welcome!
I didn't think I was gone for all
that long.
Look out!
Hello, Peter!
That's what I thought.
I'm never greeted like that.
Boing!
458 degrees north, and 561 degrees east, while
looking west.
It's Santa Claus.
I can see that.
No, it really is Santa Claus!
I admit it.
I didn't believe.
Me neither.
Hello, Santa Claus!
Are you Santa Claus?
The real Santa Claus?
Do you really live in the North Pole?
Ho, ho, ho!
Easy now, Michael.
Wow!
You know me?
How do you know who I am?
Of course I know you.
That's normal.
Everyone knows you but me.
Um, no one knows me.
I mean...
Excuse him, Mr. Santa Claus.
Sometimes he's a little too, uh, pushy.
Ho, ho, ho, ho!
Don't worry, John.
He's no bother at all.
So, Santa, still having landing problems, huh?
Ho, ho, ho, ho!
Not at all.
We did everything exactly as Stringbean and I
planned.
Isn't that right, Stringbean?
Yeah, exactly.
It was even an exceptionally successful staggered roll
landing, I'd say.
Woo-hoo!
Yeah!
Well, who wants to go for a sleigh
ride?
Yeah!
Ho, ho, ho, ho!
So, my friends, what are we waiting for?
It's all done.
Arrgh!
Well, Smee?
Not bad.
Not bad at all, Captain.
You still have to work on your tessitura
a little, but...
No, you triple nitwit!
Not the laugh, the plan!
Uh, you surprise me, Captain.
I feel like telling you it's pretty, but
I doubt that's really what you want to
hear from me.
Whatever!
I don't need your worthless opinion anyway.
Assemble the crew.
We're going to go down in history as
the pirates who stole Christmas.
And that will be the highlight of my
memoirs.
First up, kidnap Santa Claus.
And then, well, I'll tell you later.
Oh, steal Christmas?
Very well.
Okay.
You're sure about that?
Then I'll get going, I guess.
Okay, okay, since you're so sure about it.
Oh!
Arrgh!
Whoa!
What's his name?
Um, uh, Rudolph.
Is he nice?
Yes.
Can I touch him?
Yes, Michael.
Yahoo!
Stay on target.
And here we are.
So, Michael, did you like it?
Loved it!
Peter, will you watch the rein here?
I have my annual errand to run.
Sure, no problem.
We'll take care of them.
So what exactly is a staggered roll landing,
anyway?
Hey, Santa, where are you going?
Leave him alone.
He's a big boy.
Huh?
I love this thing!
Whoa-ho-ho!
Oh, Santa, how are you?
Has it been a year already?
Is it still cold in the North Pole?
Everything's fine, and I brought you a present.
A present?
You shouldn't have.
Why'd you do that?
Well, I am Santa Claus, after all.
Ho-ho-ho-ho!
The North Pole is a geographic region situated
in the Arctic Ocean.
It's talking to us!
It's covered in ice all year long.
Ho-ho-ho!
Don't get your head stuck in there now!
And then he says let's run towards the
horizon and catch an oblique beam.
Santa!
Ho-ho-ho!
It's been ages, ladies.
You look much better than you did last
year.
To say the least, Santa.
Our little Tinkerbell paid us the honor of
the visit.
And a tear.
Just what we needed to give us silky
smooth skin again.
Well, that's wonderful news.
Especially since I thought it'd be quite sad
to do my annual fairy dust harvest all
by my lonesome.
Would you do the honor of assisting me?
Of course!
There you go.
Ho-ho-ho!
Perfect!
Since you're here, Michael, maybe you could give
me a hand?
I didn't want to follow you, but I
just really, really wanted to see you some
more, and...
Why don't we discuss that a little bit
later, okay?
Yes, of course!
Ho-ho-ho!
We'll have to find another way to carry
this basket.
I have an idea.
You see?
As simple as that.
Thanks, Michael.
It's the same thing every year.
But this time, thanks to you, it will
be a whole lot easier.
Where exactly are we going?
We go where I want.
Now be quiet, a lot of you.
Pirates!
Hurry, Michael.
Take this and get out of here.
But I can't just leave you.
Michael, do what I say.
Please.
Do you really want to help me?
But...
Then go warn Peter.
Okay.
I'll go get help.
Captain, it's Santa Claus.
Of course it's Santa Claus.
We're not here by chance.
Go say hello to him.
No, no.
You do it.
I'm too shy.
Would you mind giving me your autograph?
I love what you do.
Why, of course.
We'll capture him, you bunch of incapables!
Capture Santa?
Yes.
Wait.
You're joking.
No.
Seriously, Captain?
Yes.
But why?
Why?
Because if you don't capture him immediately, I'll
make you all walk the plank one by
one!
Well, sorry about this, Santa, but you know
how it is.
Orders are orders.
Sure, orders are orders.
We don't have anything against you.
He does.
We don't really know why, but apparently he
doesn't care much for Christmas.
Well, this take long because it's not very
convenient for me, you know.
I have a very busy schedule.
Make it snappy!
You're in luck.
The Captain must be in a hurry, too.
Very good.
So, uh, where are you taking me?
This way, Santa.
If you please.
No!
Not if he pleases!
He's our prisoner!
You bodily fools!
Yeah!
Hey, how's it going?
Having fun in there?
Oh, yeah!
This bottomless trunk is brilliant!
And you drive a lot better than Santa
does, Mira.
Totally amazing!
I have to ask Santa how he made
this.
It'd be so useful for putting our things
away.
So, Michael, does this answer your question about
how Santa manages to carry so many presents
in such a small sleigh?
Michael?
Where is he?
Did anyone see Michael?
There he is!
Whoa!
Hang on, Michael!
I've got you!
Whoa!
He kidnapped Santa!
What?
How do you know that?
I told you not to follow him!
Yeah, well, it might have been a good
thing for once.
That lousy pirate!
If he touches a single hair on Santa's
white beard, he'll regret it.
I promise you.
Lost Kids, we're going to rescue Santa Claus!
How's that?
Not too loose for you?
It's good and uncomfortable, I hope.
It's perfect, Captain.
Three feet?
Five feet?
Ow!
Be quiet, would you?
Stop clowning around, you two!
Those flying vermin will be here soon, and
everything needs to be ready for them.
But it's Shallou's fault.
That's not true.
He's the one who...
I don't want to know!
Now get back to work!
Your fault.
Go ahead, if you're so smart.
Shmee!
Could you keep an eye on the work?
Because if I do it, we'll be short
of hands, and time is of the essence.
Speaking of that, Captain, I don't see why
we've captured Santa Claus.
Peter Pan will certainly come to free him.
I'm counting on it, Mr. Shmee.
I'm counting on it.
I'm ready and waiting for Peter Pan, in
a manner of speaking.
Hm.
Hm?
Hey!
Here they come, Captain!
Everything is perfect.
My plan is ready.
Perfect.
Charge!
Get him!
Release him this instant, Hook!
Of course!
Not so fast!
It's your turn!
Your choice, scoundrel!
Do you want to waste time beating me
up, or do you want to save your
precious Santa Claus?
Oh, no!
Too late!
Peter!
The sharks!
This time you've gone too far!
Over here, kids!
Help me!
It's not working!
Go!
Go, go!
Hold on!
I'll help you!
But, Captain, we're not going to let Santa
go to the sharks, are we?
Tinkerbell, do something!
Oh, yeah!
Good job, Tinkerbell!
I'm coming!
That was close!
Over here!
Are you okay?
No harm done?
Hook, you're going to get it!
Where did it go?
Um, Captain, why did we abandon the ship?
That's pretty odd, isn't it?
Kidnapping Santa was just a diversion to reach
our real goal.
We have a real goal?
If someone would have informed me there was
a real goal, I would have understood better.
Gentlemen!
We're going to take over Santa Claus's world!
Workshop!
You see now?
That's clear.
A whole lot clearer than a stupid drawing.
No one here!
No one here either.
As far as stupid plans go, they really
did it this time.
Capturing Santa to vanish at the last second?
How ridiculous!
Well, not as stupid as all that, Peter.
Because I'm really behind schedule now, I'll never
be able to deliver the presents in time.
Not if we give you a little hand.
Well, since you make such a nice offer,
I suppose a little help at the workshop
would be a good thing.
We're going to see your workshop?
The sleigh is now leaving.
Please keep your hands inside the sleigh and
don't get out until we come to a
complete stop.
Hi-ya!
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
He who laughs last, laughs longest.
We will fly all over the world, all
over the sky, all over time.